Kaido.
Far away,
but not long ago, Zoro found himself trapped
on a certain gloomy island with Perona.
The heck is this?
It looks like a grave.
The question's who made it.
Whoever they are, they've got some skill.
It was carved straight out of that tree.
I don't know if this is
good creepy or bad creepy.
Fast!
Damn it!
Strong too!
Look out!
What are those things?
This is Lazy Bones Island in
the land of poverty, Hungary.
Sent here by Kuma, Brook was mistaken
for Satan by the island's inhabitants.
How lovely, another perfect day.
You're in trouble this
time, do you hear me?
Put her down, now!
But I'm going to warn you again.
Let my daughter go!
We've had enough of this!
We'll give you a taste of hell!
Don't let them take me away!
Uh, they're really
kidnapping her, aren't they?
Uh-huh.
Unless you cursed them.
Yes, now's the time!
Never mind that!
Shouldn't we be chasing them?
Oh, I'm saving!
We're too late.
Did you hear us, Satan?
We were cheering extra hard.
You can save us now, Dark Lord.
Give it your best.
I see what got them in this
situation now. They're lazy.
But that young lady is still a victim.
I can't allow her to
suffer such a cruel fate.
I will save her.
At the very least, I owe you for the food.
Not to mention the panties.
Lord Satan!
You must forgive me, Luffy. Everyone.
Right now, I'm rather busy being
Satan in a sea of underwear.
I'm afraid our reunion will have to wait.
I owe my odd new friends
a debt of gratitude.
But I am confident that I
shall resolve this quickly.
I hope you keep safe until then.
Deep in the south blue
lies Birdie Kingdom,
where a race of giant
birds reigns supreme.
Oh, man, I really want
off this stinking island.
This place is seriously the worst.
Birds treating me like I'm their toy.
And humans constantly trying
to eat me in a hot pot.
If that's not bad
enough, and it really is,
the birds and humans won't
stop fighting each other.
There's got to be a way out of here.
Positioned deep in the Grand
Line, we find Peachy Island,
home of the Kamabaka Kingdom.
Where am I?
I wasn't even looking.
Am I safe in here?
What the hell is wrong with you psychos?
Ow, I've been waiting for you.
Hey, hold on.
Who is this bastard?
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
Dear Nami and Robin, how are you?
I hope this finds you well.
I do so look forward to
seeing the two of you again.
I'm certain that when the time comes,
We'll be better friends than ever before!
Far away but not long ago, On a
sky island known as Weatheria,
A weather wizard Or rather a weathered
scientist Continued his studies.
Young lady, over here!
A ship?
Whoa, what the heck?
It flies?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Here we go!
Oh, that's the island I was looking for.
Let's land there.
It's so dry.
You can save our island, and
we're to believe that? Huh? Yeah!
Yeah.
Thankfully, I'm an
expert with the weather.
I'll gladly summon a
shower or two. You jest.
So how about we make a little deal?
Does 100 million berries sound fair?
That's a lot!
Did I highball it a bit?
Are you kidding me?
Do they look rich to you?
I see.
Well, how does a hundred sound? Huh?
Sound cheap!
What's that?
Soap bubbles, maybe?
Looks like there's something inside.
One more thing.
Could you take this and generate
some wind for me, please?
Oh, I see.
Do you want it full power?
But of course!
Oh!
Rain clouds!
How could that be?
It's raining!
What did I tell you?
They sure are happy, aren't they?
A science of weather has
many wonderful applications.
This is the Mechanical
Island, Futureland, Baltimore?
also known as the
birthplace of the genius.
We better get him to the hospital, Kevin.
Yeah.
Well, he's definitely a cyborg.
I can't believe he runs on cola.
What should we do?
We don't have any sodas to refuel him.
There's no time to lose.
We need to begin. Right.
Hello, you're the young
lad from earlier, correct?
I do hope I haven't kept
you waiting for too long.
Yeah, you're definitely different.
What did they do to you? Well,
it seems the cola is hard to come by here,
so they brewed up some
fine hot tea instead.
Dodge healing, to be precise.
Hot tea?
Mmm.
The aroma and flavor are truly super.
Lovely.
There's really nothing quite so relaxing.
Okay if you say so I'm
sorry where are my manners?
Enjoy careful it's hot.
No no this is weird it's all wrong.
Hey mister you're not funny now I
liked you more the way you were.
Oh is that so?
It's cold.
How on earth did I end up
out here in the elements?
Huh?
Ah, how lovely.
A scarf for me.
Thanks.
Goodness, this, this is a nightmare.
Keep out.
This is an enclosed forest
of mechanical animals.
Ready for plan A's.
Surprise awakening in the
jungle nothing's more wild than
mecca animals this will get
him back on track for sure now
now let's calm down shall
we friends because you seem
agitated this morning did you
remember to eat your breakfast it
is the most important meal of
the day you know let's work
on getting those blood sugar
levels up hold on a second that
means it's breakfast time
for me too you silly goose
delicious
no
better way to start
the day than with a cup of tea
let's cherish every moment
friends it's not working?
Someone help us!
Mama, violence is never the end.
I know you're at an age
where you want to be not.
But listen, we can sort
this out like gentlemen.
Nothing good ever comes.
Awful violence.
Come on, just fight back, please.
You can't reason with gorillas.
Relax.
Listen to words.
Listen to what I have to.
If you'd let me talk, I
have wisdom to impart.
My friend, we must...
We...
Oh, yeah!
Super!
What do you think I am,
you punks? Chopped liver?
You can't step to Franky!
He's back!
You are seriously starting
to scare me! Oh, yeah!
Wow!
I cooled off a bit and ran
out of steam. Literally.
Huh?
You mean, you're gonna turn back?
No!
I know just the place to go!
My grandpa told me there's
some dangerous stuff in there.
But it's an emergency and I have you
to protect me, so it should be okay.
Here's your breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
Once you finish that, we'll
get back to our questioning.
Oh, I can hardly wait.
Not to intrude, but it sounds like
you've been hurt pretty bad, young lady.
Who?
Just a decrepit old man.
I've only been in this
country for a single day now,
but the guards in charge
said the elderly are useless?
so they promptly threw me in here.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
What the?!
There's a band of dissidents running wild!
The warden called for backup!
He ordered all of us to get over there!
Sir!
A band of dissidents? Yes, sir.
But we were quick to
follow your orders, sir.
All teams descended on the group
so it didn't get out of hand.
What are you talking about?
I didn't give any orders!
Don't tell me.
When you say all teams, Do you mean the
soldiers stationed at the prison tower?
I'm an agent working for
the Revolutionary Army.
You fool!
You really think I give a
damn about the dissonance?
Take down Mock Robin on site, men!
Good work.
With your command of our
forces, I know we can win.
Well, you can count on me.
Release the young lady from her cell.
Well, she's already been
through enough as it is.
And clutch!
The Nico Robin?
Whoa, what the hell is this place?
It smells so good.
Oh, and he bumps when
you got stuff like this.
Ramen falls in.
Spaghetti patches in.
Ham fruits in.
Chocolate rocks in.
Take whatever you want.
It's all safe to eat.
Ow!
So I'm okay to eat this too, right?
Right. Yum-yum. Eat your fill.
Once you've had enough
to build up your stamina,
the man-eating plan's in one
mess with you. Sure, right.
Good plan.
This stuff is so good, I feel
like I could eat forever.
Eating's only the first step.
You've gotta exercise, too.
Well, yeah, obviously.
But I'm still on the first step here.
I gotta bulk up so I can become a cool
hero of the forest like you, right?
Oh, man, I can't eat another bite.
Ooh, sopping.
Don't you realize fat things are the first
creatures to be eaten on this island?
Wait, are you talking about me?
It's impossible to escape
from the Bowen Islands.
Why didn't you tell me that before?
As for me, I'm the hero
of the first round!